

# Clare Lim Full Stack Developer

lhy.clare@gmail.com

portfolio-clare.herokuapp.com

linkedin.com/in/clare-lhy

github.com/clarelhy

More than 5 years of experience in a fast-paced environment, trained in hell and always ready to get my hands dirty in the face of challenges. I thrive when given autonomy and freedom to explore and innovate. I work efficiently when trusted to manage and deliver under minimal supervision, both collaboratively and independently. Check out my LinkedIn and web portfolio to know more!

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**Full Stack Developer** IDEMIA Singapore Pte Ltd

03/2021 - Present

- Full Stack Developer in SCRUM Turn-key Project Team
- Running SCRUM for border-control turn-key projects
- Web App development with Angular 11 and Node.js
- iOS App development with React Native and Node.js
- CI/CD with GitLab and JIRA, using FastLane for iOS Apps
- Manage and guide interns with development work

# Full Stack Software Engineer

ST Engineering Mission Software & Services Pte Ltd

11/2016 - 03/2021

- Team Lead in SCRUM Turn-key Project Team
- Experienced in C2 / C3 Systems, Module Lead for 2D Map Product
- Full stack development with AngularJS and Node.js for various systems as Module Lead, Team Lead or Project Developer
- Delivered and maintained 2D Map Product for in-house framework
- Delivered and maintained 8 Operations Monitoring Systems (See portfolio linked above for more details)
- Worked directly with PM, BA, UI/UX, clients, BD and pre-sales
- Managed both local and offshore development teams

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science, Double Major in Computer Science, Cyber Forensics & Information Security and Management

Murdoch University

05/2015 - 09/2016

Diploma in Infocomm and Network Engineering Temasek Polytechnic

05/2012 - 05/2015

# **SKILLS**

**SCRUM** Full Stack Development Angular 1 / 2+ Node.js **REST API** CI/CD JavaScript / TypeScript FastLane NoSQL GitLab / JIRA React / React Native 2D GIS Map

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

ST Top Talent Group (2019 - 2021)

Director's List Award (2014)

#### **LANGUAGES**

#### English

Full Professional Proficiency

#### Chinese

Full Professional Proficiency

#### Cantonese

Professional Working Proficiency

#### **INTERESTS**

Tattoo Gaming Music Arcade Space Exploration Xeno/Archaeology